List<Map<String, dynamic>> beginner = [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the past tense of 'eat'?",
    "answer": "ate",
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the present continuous tense of 'go'?",
    "answer": "going",
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the future tense of 'run'?",
    "answer": "will run",
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the present perfect tense of 'drink'?",
    "answer": "have drunk",
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is the past continuous tense of 'sleep'?",
    "answer": "was sleeping",
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the past tense of 'read'?",
    "answer": "read",
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is the present tense of 'write'?",
    "answer": "write",
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the future tense of 'sing'?",
    "answer": "will sing",
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the present perfect tense of 'do'?",
    "answer": "have done",
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is the past continuous tense of 'eat'?",
    "answer": "was eating",
  }
];
List<Map<String, dynamic>> medium = [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the past tense of 'speak'?",
    "answer": "spoke",
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the present continuous tense of 'run'?",
    "answer": "is running",
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the future tense of 'write'?",
    "answer": "will write",
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the present perfect tense of 'take'?",
    "answer": "have taken",
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is the past continuous tense of 'swim'?",
    "answer": "was swimming",
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the past tense of 'think'?",
    "answer": "thought",
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is the present tense of 'drive'?",
    "answer": "drive",
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the future tense of 'dance'?",
    "answer": "will dance",
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the present perfect tense of 'see'?",
    "answer": "have seen",
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is the past continuous tense of 'drink'?",
    "answer": "was drinking",
  }
];
List<Map<String, dynamic>> expert = [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the past tense of 'begin'?",
    "answer": "began",
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the present continuous tense of 'fly'?",
    "answer": "is flying",
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the future tense of 'give'?",
    "answer": "will give",
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the present perfect tense of 'fall'?",
    "answer": "have fallen",
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is the past continuous tense of 'fall'?",
    "answer": "was falling",
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the past tense of 'wear'?",
    "answer": "wore",
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is the present tense of 'lead'?",
    "answer": "lead",
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the future tense of 'leave'?",
    "answer": "will leave",
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the present perfect tense of 'buy'?",
    "answer": "have bought",
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is the past continuous tense of 'come'?",
    "answer": "was coming",
  }
];